Department of Physics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Physics summer school, 1966 - 1975; F-19-15; 30 cm of textual records
  - Physics summer school 1970, 1969 - 1971; F-19-15-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 19-10)
  - Physics summer school 1970, 1969 - 1971; F-19-15-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 19-10)
  - Physics summer school 1970, 1969 - 1971; F-19-15-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 19-10)
  - NATO advanced summer institute 1970, 1969 - 1971; F-19-15-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 19-10)
  - NATO advanced summer institute 1970, 1969 - 1971; F-19-15-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
  - NATO advanced summer institute 1970, 1969 - 1971; F-19-15-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
  - NATO advanced summer institute 1970, 1969 - 1971; F-19-15-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
  - NATO advanced summer institute 1970, F-19-15-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
  - NATO advanced summer institute 1970, F-19-15-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
  - Physics summer school 1974, 1973 - 1975; F-19-15-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
  - Physics summer school 1974, 1973 - 1975; F-19-15-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
  - Physics summer school 1974, 1973 - 1975; F-19-15-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
  - Physics summer school 1974, F-19-15-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
  - Physics summer school 1974, F-19-15-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 19-11)
- Chairman's correspondence, 1971 - 1986; F-19-16; 61 cm of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence sent or received by the Chair of the Physics Department. Outgoing correspondence was arranged chronologically. The series includes memoranda and reports.
  - J. F. Cochran, 1971 - 1972; F-19-16-1; 7 cm of textual records
    - J.F. Cochran - chair's correspondence, 1971; F-19-16-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
    - J.F. Cochran - chair's correspondence, 1971; F-19-16-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
    - J.F. Cochran - chair's correspondence, 1971; F-19-16-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
    - J.F. Cochran - chair's correspondence, 1971; F-19-16-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
    - J.F. Cochran - chair's correspondence, 1972; F-19-16-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
    - J.F. Cochran - chair's correspondence, 1972; F-19-16-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
  - Correspondence - University administration, 1977 - 1986; F-19-16-2; 6 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence with University administration, 1977 - 1980; F-19-16-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
    - Correspondence with University administration, 1980 - 1983; F-19-16-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
    - Correspondence with University administration (cont'd), 1980 - 1983; F-19-16-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
    - Correspondence with University administration, 1983 - 1986; F-19-16-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
    - Correspondence with University administration (cont'd), 1983 - 1986; F-19-16-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-12)
  - Correspondence - Dean of Science, 1977 - 1986; F-19-16-3; 8 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1977 - 1980; F-19-16-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1980; F-19-16-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1981; F-19-16-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1981; F-19-16-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1982; F-19-16-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1982; F-19-16-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1983; F-19-16-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1983; F-19-16-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1984 - 1985; F-19-16-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - Correspondence with Dean of Science, 1985 - 1986; F-19-16-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1972 - 1977; F-19-16-4; 41 cm of textual records
    - To President, 1974 - 1977; F-19-16-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - To Vice-President, Academic and Associate Vice-President Academic, 1974 - 1977; F-19-16-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - To Dean of Science, 1974; F-19-16-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - To Dean of Science, 1975; F-19-16-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - To Dean of Science, 1976; F-19-16-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-13)
    - To Dean of Science, 1977; F-19-16-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - To Faculty in Department, 1974; F-19-16-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - To Faculty in Department, 1975; F-19-16-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - To Faculty in Department, 1976; F-19-16-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - To Faculty in Department, 1977; F-19-16-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Re Grad. Student Inquiry Correspondence, 1972 - 1973; F-19-16-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Re Grad. Student Inquiry Correspondence, 1974; F-19-16-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1973; F-19-16-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1973; F-19-16-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1973; F-19-16-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1973; F-19-16-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1973; F-19-16-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1974; F-19-16-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1974; F-19-16-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 19-14)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1974; F-19-16-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1975; F-19-16-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1976; F-19-16-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Internal Correspondence (Department and University), 1977; F-19-16-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1972; F-19-16-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1972; F-19-16-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1972; F-19-16-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1972; F-19-16-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1972; F-19-16-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1973; F-19-16-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1973; F-19-16-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1973; F-19-16-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1973; F-19-16-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1973; F-19-16-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1973; F-19-16-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 19-15)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1974; F-19-16-4-0-35 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1974; F-19-16-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1974; F-19-16-4-0-37 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1974; F-19-16-4-0-38 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1974; F-19-16-4-0-39 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1974; F-19-16-4-0-40 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1975; F-19-16-4-0-41 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1975; F-19-16-4-0-42 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1975; F-19-16-4-0-43 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1976; F-19-16-4-0-44 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1976; F-19-16-4-0-45 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1976; F-19-16-4-0-46 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1977; F-19-16-4-0-47 (Archival box - standard 19-16)
    - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1977; F-19-16-4-0-48 (Archival box - standard 19-16)